[BLOG](https://blog.goodtodo.com/)  _/_  [SIGN UP](#signup-popup)  _/_  [Log in](#login-popup)

Good Todo Privacy Policy
========================

Welcome to Good Todo!

1. Company
    
    Goodtodo.com is owned and run by Creative Good Projects, LLC ("Creative Good"). To contact us with questions about this privacy policy, please contact us via our Contact form at [https://creativegood.com/contact/](https://creativegood.com/contact/) or via postal mail at Creative Good Projects, LLC, c/o Jerry S. Goldman, Esq., Anderson Kill P.C., 1251 Avenue of the Americas, New York, NY 10020, USA (+1.212.278.1000).
    
2. Scope
    
    Creative Good Projects, LLC, d/b/a goodtodo.com ("goodtodo.com"), has adopted this Privacy Policy to inform its customers and others about how it protects personally identifiable information and other information that may be collected when customers use the Good Todo service.
    
    This Privacy Policy covers Creative Good's treatment of personal or personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that may be collected when you are on the goodtodo.com website, and when you use the mobile apps or any other Good Todo services. The privacy of your nonpublic information is important to us. This includes, but is not limited to, your name, email address and any other personally identifiable information. We use safeguards to protect your privacy and confidentiality. This Policy Statement discusses information we collect and the manner in which it is used.
    
3. Sharing and Disclosure of Personal Information
    
    We are committed to your privacy. **Creative Good will not sell or rent your Personal Information to any individual, business, or government entity. Since our business is based on subscriptions, we have no interest in sharing your Personal Information.** However, Creative Good will share your Personal Information with other entities if Creative Good is required to respond to court orders, subpoenas, or other legal process. Creative Good may also use customer identifiable information to troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, or investigate and help prevent potentially unlawful activity or activity that threatens Goodtodo.com's customers or otherwise violates the Terms of Use.
    
4. Information We Collect
    
    We will store your name and e-mail address if you sign up for a goodtodo.com account. If you upgrade to a paid account via the website with a credit card, we will encrypt your credit card number and transmit it to Authorize.net, where it will be stored. Our servers do not store your full card number. We store encrypted versions of the last four digits of the card number, the expiration date, and card type. We also, of course, store your todos and any other data that you enter into your goodtodo.com account (via email, the website, or the iOS mobile app). We use cookies to identify return users, so that they need not log in each time they arrive. All data we collect is stored on servers located in the United States.

    Other information we collect:
    
    * Website: When you access Goodtodo.com, your Web browser automatically transmits to our servers your IP address, as well as the page address you are accessing. Creative Good does not use that information except in the aggregate, to help us identify the Good Todo features that customers use the most. **The goodtodo.com website does not use third-party trackers such as those created by Google and Facebook.**
        
    * Mobile apps: The Good Todo mobile apps do not capture any additional data except anonymous crash data for crash-log reporting, so that we can identify if the app has a bug that needs to be fixed. Our mobile apps do not access users' location, camera, or microphone; nor do they employ any other tracking or surveillance. However, outside of Creative Good's control, the mobile apps may include tracking employed by Apple or Google that may be built into their iOS and Android mobile operating systems.
        
5. Account cancellation and deletion
    * Account cancellation: You can cancel your account any time by using the Cancel My Account link available on the Preferences page on the goodtodo.com website.
        
    * Account deletion: If you use the Cancel My Account feature, or if your renewal date passes without a renewal payment, your account and all associated data will be fully deleted after a "grace period," which allows users to renew their account data for a period after the renewal date. However, if you wish for your account data to be deleted more quickly, contact Creative Good via our Contact form at [https://creativegood.com/contact/](https://creativegood.com/contact/) and request the deletion of your cancelled account. We will delete the account and all associated data from the goodtodo.com site, then confirm with you once it is done. Your data will also be deleted from our backup servers as they complete the full rotation of their rolling backups in several days. To delete your data from your local mobile device, simply delete the Good Todo mobile app from the device.
        
6. Access
    
    We restrict access to nonpublic information to Good Todo developers who need to access that information in order to provide goodtodo.com service to you.
    
7. Lawful Use of Services
    
    Good Todo services may only be used for lawful purposes. Transmission of any material in violation of any US or state or local law, rule, or regulation is strictly prohibited. This includes, but is not limited to: copyrighted or trademarked material; material legally judged to be threatening or obscene; material protected by trade secret; or material which violates a legally protected privacy right of an individual. Persons under the age of 18 may access goodtodo.com only with involvement of a parent or guardian.
    
8. Amendments
    
    Creative Good will keep this policy current and reserves the right to change this policy at any time by amending the content of this Statement. Creative Good will post a notice of changes on the goodtodo.com website, when and if the policy is amended. This Statement and the policies expressed herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any customer, user, or other third party.
    
9. Ownership
    
    Goodtodo.com is the exclusive trade name and mark of Creative Good Projects, LLC.

    Effective August 21, 2018

Log in
------

 Remember me

Sign Up
-------

By submitting, you are indicating you have read our [Terms of use](https://goodtodo.com/main/terms/).

Already registered? [Log in](#login-popup)

Submit[](#confirm-popup)

Confirmation
============

You've just been sent an email to confirm your email address.

Please follow the instructions to confirm your account.

[Click here](#) to return to the site

Confirmation
============

You've just been sent an email.

Please follow the instructions to reset your password.

[Click here](#) to return to the site

­
